--==本字幕由 美剧台词网 逐行精校==--
详细台词讲解 请访问 fluensay.net
老友记
第一季第一集
没人告诉你生活会是这样
So no one told you life was gonna be this way
你滑稽的工作  你的差劲
your jobs a joke, you're broke,
你半途而废的爱情
your love life's D.O.A.
就像开车卡在二档
It's like you're always stuck in second gear,
每日每周每月
And it hasn't been your day, your week, your month,
甚至每年都是如此
or even your year, but
大雨倾盆时
I'll be there for you,
我会陪伴你
when the rain starts to pour.
I'll be there for you,
像我以前那样
like I've been there before.
我会陪伴你
I'll be there for you,
因为你也陪伴着我
'cause you're there for me too.
中央咖啡馆
There's nothing to tell!
这没什么好说的
He's just some guy I work with!
他不过是我的同事
C'mon, you're going out with the guy!
少来了  你们都在约会了
There's gotta be something wrong with him!
这个男人一定有什么问题
So does he have a hump? A hump and a hairpiece?
他是驼背吗  戴着假发的驼背
Wait, does he eat chalk?
等等  他吃粉笔吗
Just, 'cause, I don't want her to go through
我只是不想你
what I went through with Carl
重蹈我和卡尔的覆辙
Okay, everybody relax. This is not even a date.
拜托各位  放松点  这甚至不算是约会
It's just two people going out to dinner
只不过是两个人出去吃个饭
and not having sex.
而且不会上床
Sounds like a date to me.
听起来像是和我约会
Alright, so I'm back in high school,
于是我回到了高中学校
I'm standing in the middle of the cafeteria
我站在食堂中间
and I realize I am totally naked.
然后发现自己全身赤裸
Oh, yeah. Had that dream.
噢  做过那种梦
Then I look down, and I realize there's a phone
然后我低下头  看见那里有一部
there.
大哥大
- Instead of...?  - That's right.
-那话儿变成了  -没错
- Never had that dream. - No.
-这种梦倒从未做过  -没有
All of a sudden, the phone starts to ring.
突然  那电话响起来了
And it turns out it's my mother,
结果是我妈打来的
which is very-very weird because-
这非常非常奇怪
she never calls me!
因为她从来不打电话给我
Hi.
嗨
This guy says hello, I wanna kill myself.
这家伙一张嘴打招呼  我就想自杀
You okay, sweetie?
你还好吧  亲爱的
I just feel like someone reached down my throat
我感觉有人把手伸入我的喉咙
grabbed my small intestine,
抓住我的小肠
pulled it out of my mouth
从我嘴里扯出来
and tied it around my neck...
然后缠在我脖子上
Cookie?
饼干
Carol moved her stuff out today
卡罗尔今天把她的东西搬走了
- Let me get you some coffee.  - Thanks.
-我帮你泡杯咖啡  -谢了
No, no don't! Stop cleansing my aura!
不  不要  别再净化我的灵气了
No, just leave my aura alone, okay?
求你了  别碰我的灵气  好吗
I'll be fine, alright?
我会没事的  好吧
Really, everyone. I hope  she'll be very happy.
真的  各位  我希望她能幸福
- No you don't. - No I don't,
-不  你不会  -没错  我不会的
to hell with her, she left me!
去她的  她甩掉了我
And you never knew she was a lesbian...
你又不知道她是女同性恋
No!! Okay?!
不知道  行了吧
Why does everyone keep fixating on that?
为何大家都绕着这个话题打转
She didn't know, how should I know?
她都不知道  我怎么会知道
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian...
有时我希望自己也是个女同性恋
Did I say that out loud?
我大声说出来了么
Alright Ross, look.
好了罗斯  瞧
You're feeling a lot of pain right now.
你现在很痛苦
You're angry. You're hurting.
你很生气  很伤心
Can I tell you what the answer is?
要不要我给你支一招
Strip joint!
脱衣舞俱乐部
C'mon, you're single! Have some hormones!
别这样  作为光棍儿  爷们起来
I don't want to be single, okay?
我不想单身的  好吗
I just...I just wanna be married again!
我只想  再次结婚
And I just want a million dollars!
而我只想要一百万美金
Rachel?!
瑞秋
Oh,God, Monica, hi! Thank God!
噢  天啊  莫妮卡  嗨  谢天谢地
I just went to your building and you weren't there
我刚去了你家  可你不在
and then this guy with a big hammer said you might be here
有个拿大锤子的家伙说你可能会在这儿
and you are, you are!
结果你真的在这儿 你真的在这儿
- Can I get you some coffee?  - De-Caff
-要来杯咖啡吗  -无咖啡因的
Okay, everybody, this is Rachel,
好了  各位  这是瑞秋
another Lincoln High survivor.
另一位林肯高中的幸存者
This is everybody, this is Chandler,
这就是各位啦  这是钱德勒
and Phoebe, and Joey,
菲比  还有乔伊
and you remember my brother Ross?
还记得我哥哥罗斯吗
- Hi, sure! - Hi.
-当然  嗨  -嗨
So you wanna tell us now
你是想现在跟我们说说
or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
还是我们再等四位湿漉漉的伴娘过来
Oh, God...well,
噢  上帝  好吧
it started about a half hour before the wedding.
大概在婚礼前半个小时
I was in the room where we were keeping all the presents,
我当时在存放礼品的房间里
and I was looking at this gravy boat.
看着调味汁瓶
This really gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.
那是一件极其美丽的里摩日细瓷调味汁瓶
When all of a sudden
然后  突然间
Sweet 'n' Lo?
有糖吗
I realized that I was more turned on
我发现我对这个调味汁瓶
by this gravy boat than by Barry!
比巴瑞更能引发我的兴奋感
And then I got really freaked out,
然后我真的吓坏了
and that's when it hit me:
突然想到
how much Barry looks like Mr. Potato Head.
巴瑞真的超像薯头先生
Y'know, I mean, I always knew he looked familiar,
我是说  我总是觉得他眼熟
but...
但是
Anyway, I just had to get out of there,
不管怎么说  我必须离开那里
and I started wondering
我开始想
"Why am I doing this, and who am I doing this for?"
"我干吗这么做  我这么做是为了谁"
So anyway I just didn't know where to go,
不管怎么说  我不知该去哪里
and I know that you and I have kinda drifted apart,
而且我知道我们有点疏远了
but you're the only person I knew
但是  你是我在这个城市
who lived here in the city.
唯一认识的人
Who wasn't invited to the wedding.
还没有被邀请参加婚礼
Ooh, I was kinda hoping that wouldn't be an issue...
噢  我希望这不是个问题
Now I'm guessing that he bought her the big pipe organ,
我猜他送她一台管风琴
and she's really not happy about it.
而她很不喜欢
Daddy, I just... I can't marry him!
爸爸  我只是  不能嫁给他
I'm sorry. I just don't love him.
对不起  我只是不爱他
Well, it matters to me!
可是对我来说就有关系
Ooh, she should not be wearing those pants.
噢  她真不应该穿那条裤子
I say push her down the stairs.
要我说  推她下楼
Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs!
推她下楼  把推她下楼  把推她下楼
C'mon Daddy, listen to me!
爸  你听我说
It's like, it's like, all of my life,
这就好像  在我一生中
everyone has always told me, 'You're a shoe!
所有人都一直告诉我"你是一只鞋子
You're a shoe, you're a shoe, you're a shoe!'.
你是鞋子  你是鞋子  你是鞋子
And today I just stopped and I said,
可今天我停下来说
'What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
"如果我不想成为一只鞋呢"
What if I wanna be a- a purse, y'know? Or a- or a hat!
如果我想当一个包包  或是一顶帽子呢
No, I don't want you to buy me a hat,
不  我不是要你给我买帽子
I'm saying I am a ha-
我说我是一顶帽子
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
这是比喻啦  爸爸
You can see where he'd have trouble.
这就是他的问题所在了
Look Daddy, it's my life.
听着爸爸  这是我的人生
Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
也许我可以和莫妮卡住在一起
Well, I guess we've established she's staying here with Monica...
我猜和莫妮卡一起住的人选已然敲定了
Well, maybe that's my decision.
也许那是我的决定
Well, maybe I don't need your money.
也许我不需要你的钱
Wait!! Wait, I said maybe!!
等等我说也许
Just breathe, breathe...that's it.
深呼吸
Just try to think of nice calm things...
就这样试着想些美好平静的事物
Rain drops on roses and rabbits and kittens
玫瑰上的雨滴  小兔子和小猫咪
doorbells and sleighbells and something with mittens...
还有门铃  雪橇铃  和啥啥的手套
La la la something with string.
啦啦啦  啥啥和绳子串起的面条
These are a few...
还有一些
I'm all better now.
我现在好多了
I helped!
我帮上忙啦
Okay, look, this is probably for the best, y'know?
瞧  或许这样反倒最好
Independence. Taking control of your life.
你独立了  可以主宰自己的人生
And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey.
如有任何需求  尽管来找乔伊
Me and Chandler live right across the hall.
我和钱德勒就住在对面
And he's away a lot.
而且他经常不在家
Joey, stop hitting on her!
乔伊  别再勾引她了
It's her wedding day!
今天是她结婚的日子
What, like there's a rule or something?
怎么啦  难道还有什么明文规定不成
Please don't do that again, it's a horrible sound.
请不要在这么干了  这声音很烦人
It's, uh, it's Paul.
我是保罗
Buzz him in.
让他进来
- Who's Paul? - Paul the Wine Guy, Paul?
-保罗是谁  -调酒的那个保罗吗
Maybe.
也许吧
Wait a minute. Your 'not a real date' tonight
等等  你今晚的"非正式约会"对象
is with Paul the Wine Guy?
是调酒师保罗
- He finally asked you out?  - Yes!
-他终于开口约你了吗  -是的
Ooh, this is a Dear Diary moment.
噢  这真是值得永久铭记的时刻
Rach, wait, I can cancel...
瑞秋  我可以取消
Please, no, go, I'll be fine!
不  你去吧我没事
Uh Ross, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?
罗斯  你没事吧你要我留下来吗
That'd be good...
那样最好
- Really? - No, go on!
-真的吗  -才怪 去吧
It's Paul the Wine Guy!
那可是调酒师保罗
Hi, come in! Paul, this is...
嗨  请进  保罗  这是
...everybody, everybody, this is Paul.
大家  各位  这是保罗
- Hey! Paul! - Hello!
-嘿  保罗  -你好
Hi! The Wine Guy!
嗨  调酒师
I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name. Paul, was it?
抱歉  没听清你的名字  保罗  是吗
Okay, sit down. Two seconds.
好了  坐会  马上就好
Ooh, I just pulled out four eyelashes. That can't be good.
噢  我刚拔掉四根睫毛  不是好兆头
So Rachel, what're you, uh... what're you up to tonight?
瑞秋  你  你今晚打算怎么过
Well, I was kinda supposed to be
这个嘛  本来我应该
headed for Aruba on my honeymoon, so nothing!
在阿鲁巴岛度蜜月  所以  没事做
Right, you're not even getting your honeymoon, God..
对哦  你都不能去度蜜月  上帝
No, no, although, Aruba, this time of year... talk about your
不过在阿鲁巴岛的这个时候  说到你的
big lizards...
大蜥蜴
Anyway, if you don't feel like being alone tonight,
不管怎样如果你今晚不想独处的话
Joey and Chandler are coming over to help me
乔伊和钱德勒要到我那儿
put together my new furniture.
帮我组合新家具
Yes, and we're very excited about it.
是呀  我们特别期待特别兴奋
Well actually thanks,
真的很感谢
but I think I'm just gonna hang out here tonight.
不过我今晚想待在这儿
- It's been a long day. - Oh, sure. Okay, sure.
-今天真的很漫长  -好吧  当然了
Hey, Pheebs, you wanna help?
菲比你想来帮忙吗
Oh, I wish I could, but I don't want to.
我倒希望能去帮忙  但我不想去
I'm supposed to attach a brackety thing to the side things,
我应该用一套这样的小蜗杆
using a bunch of these little worm guys.
将托架装在侧面
I have no brackety thing, I see no worm guys whatsoever
但我没看见托架  也没有看见什么蜗杆
and I cannot feel my legs.
而且我的腿麻了
What's this?
这是什么
I have no idea.
我也不知道
- Done with the bookcase!  - All finished!
-书架做好了  -全部完工
This was Carol's favorite beer.
这是卡罗尔最爱喝的啤酒
She always drank it out of the can, I should have known.
她总是不用易拉罐喝  我该知道
Ross, let me ask you a question.
罗斯  我问你一个问题
She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV-
她得到了家具  音响和很棒的电视机
what did you get?
你得到什么
You guys.
你们
- Oh, my God. - You got screwed.
-天啊  -你被坑了
Oh my God!
天哪
- Oh my God! - I know, I know, I'm such an idiot.
-天哪  -我知道  我是个大白痴
I guess I should have caught on when
她每周看四五次牙医时
she started going to the dentist four and five times a week.
我心里就该有数了
I mean, how clean can teeth get?
我是说  牙齿能需要多干净呢
My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess.
我哥也碰到这种事了  他也很纠结
How did you get through it?
你是怎么熬过来的
Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers,
你可以尝试  不小心砸烂她贵重的东西
- say her... - ...leg?
-比如她的  -腿
That's one way of going through it, yeah. Me, I-
那也是种选择  至于我嘛
I went for the watch.
我砸烂了她的表
You actually broke her watch?
你真的把她的表弄坏了
Barry, I'm sorry... I am so sorry...
巴瑞  对不起  真是对不起
I know you probably think that this is all about
你一定认为这件事跟
what I said the other day about you making love with your socks on,
我那天说你穿着袜子做爱有关
but it isn't... it isn't, it's about me, and I just...
其实不是  是我的原因  我只是
Hi, machine cut me off again...
喂  电话又断了
anyway...look, look,
不管怎样  听着
You know what the scariest part is?
你知道最可怕的是什么
What if there's only one woman for everybody, y'know?
万一人这一辈子只有一个女人怎么办
I mean what if you get one woman-
我是说如果你找了个女人
and that's it?
然后就此过一生
Unfortunately in my case, there was only one woman- for her...
不幸的是  我唯一的女人爱的是  女人
What are you talking about? 'One woman'?
你说什么呢  "一个女人"
That's like saying there's only one flavor of ice cream for you.
这就像是在说  你只能吃一种冰淇淋口味
Lemme tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavors out there.
让我告诉你  罗斯  还有很多种口味
There's Rocky Road, and Cookie Dough, and Bing! Cherry Vanilla.
有巧克力坚果味  曲奇味还有香草味
You could get 'em with Jimmies, or nuts, or whipped cream!
还可以和糖条  果仁  或者奶油一起吃
This is the best thing that ever happened to you!
这简直是你一生中最大的喜事
You got married, you were, like, what, eight?
你难道是八岁结的婚吗
Welcome back to the world! Grab a spoon!
欢迎回到现实世界  拿起勺子开挖吧
I honestly don't know if I'm hungry or horny.
我真不晓得现在自己是真饿了还是欲火难耐
Stay out of my freezer!
离我的冰箱远点
Ever since she walked out on me, I, uh...
自从她甩掉我之后  我就
What?... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?
怎么了  你打算边搅面条边讲吗
No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.
不  这该是第五次约会时候才说的事儿
Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?
噢  这么说会有第五次约会了
Isn't there?
你不想吗
Yeah... yeah, I think there is.
想  我想的
What were you gonna say?
你刚才想说什么
Well, ever-ev-... ever since she left me,
好吧  自从她离开后
um, I haven't been able to, uh, perform.
我就一直无法过
...Sexually.
性生活
Oh, God, Oh, God, I am sorry...
天啊  天啊  对不起
- I am so sorry... - It's okay...
-真不好意思  -没事  没事
I know being spit on is probably not what you need right now.
我知道你现在需要的必然不是被人喷一身水
- Um... how long? - Two years.
-多久了  -两年了
Wow! I'm-I'm-I'm glad you smashed her watch!
我真高兴你砸烂了她的表
So you still think you, um... might want that fifth date?
那你还想要第五次约会吗
...Yeah. Yeah, I do.
是的  我希望有
Oh...see... but Joanne loved Chachi!
看  乔安妮是爱卡奇的
That's the difference!
这就是不同
Grab a spoon.
"拿起勺子"
Do you know how long it's been since I've grabbed a spoon?
你知道我拿起勺子多久了吗
Do the words 'Billy, don't be a hero' mean anything to you?
难道"比利  别逞英雄"这句话对你没意义
《比利  别逞英雄》  70年代反战歌曲
Y'know, here's the thing.
还有个问题
Even if I could get it together enough to- to ask a woman out,...
就算我鼓足了勇气  想约个女人出来
who am I gonna ask?
我又能约谁呢
Isn't this amazing?
不可思议吧
I mean, I have never made coffee before in my entire life.
我这辈子从没泡过咖啡
- That is amazing. - Congratulations.
-真不可思议  -恭喜你了
While you're on a roll
既然你现在正进入角色
If you feel like you gotta make, like a Western omelet or something..
有没有想做个煎蛋卷之类的东西
Although actually I'm really not that hungry...
不过事实上我还不太饿
- Morning. - Good morning.
-早安  -早安
- Morning. - Morning, Paul.
-早安  -早安  保罗
- Hello, Paul. - Hi, Paul, is it?
-你好保罗  -嗨  保罗是吧
- Thank you. Thank you so much. - Stop.
-谢谢  太感谢你了  -不要这样
We'll talk later.
晚点联系
Yeah. Thank you.
谢谢你
That wasn't a real date?!
那还不叫真正的约会
What the hell do you do on a real date?
那你真正的约会到底要干些什么
- Shut up, and put my table back. - Okayyy!
-闭嘴  把桌子抬回去  -好啦
All right, kids, I gotta get to work.
好了孩子们  我必须上班去了
If I don't input those numbers...
但如果我不输入那些数字
it doesn't make much of a difference...
也没什么关系
So, like, you guys all have jobs?
你们大伙儿都有工作
Yeah, we all have jobs.
对  我们都有工作
See, that's how we buy stuff.
这样才有钱买东西
Yeah, I'm an actor.
对  我是个演员
Wow! Would I have seen you in anything?
你演过什么  我看过吗
I doubt it. Mostly regional work.
难说  大部分范围都挺小的
Oh wait, wait, unless you happened to catch the
等下  除非你碰巧看过
Reruns' production of Pinocchio.
《匹诺曹》的重播
'Look, Gippetto, I'm a real live boy.'
"瞧  盖佩多  我是真正的小男孩了"
《匹诺曹》的剧中台词
-  I will not take this abuse.  - You're right, I'm sorry.
-别这么侮辱人  -你说得对  对不起
"Once I was a wooden boy, a little wooden boy..."
"我曾是个小木偶  小木偶"
So how you doing today?
今天感觉如何
Did you sleep okay? Talk to Barry?
睡得还好吧  跟巴瑞谈过了吗
I can't stop smiling.
我无法停止笑
I can see that.
看得出来
You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.
你活像昨晚睡觉时嘴里放了个撑衣架
I know, he's just so, so...
我知道  他是那么
Do you remember you and Tony DeMarco?
还记得你和托尼·德马科吗
Oh, yeah.
记得啊
Well, it's like that. With feelings.
就像那样  那种感觉
- Wow,are you in trouble!
-哇  你真是有麻烦了
Okay. Okay. I am just going to get up, go to work
好啦  好啦  我要站起来  去工作
and not think about him all day.
而且一整天都不要想他
Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.
或者只是站起来去工作
- Oh, look, wish me luck! - What for?
-祝我好运  -为什么
I'm gonna go get one of those job things.
我要去找那个工作什么的东西
Hey, Monica!
嘿  莫妮卡
Hey Frannie, welcome back!
嘿  弗兰妮  欢迎回来
How was Florida?
在佛罗里达过得如何
You had sex, didn't you?
你做爱了  对不
- How do you do that?
-你怎么知道的
So? Who?
那么  和谁
You know Paul?
你认识保罗吧
Paul the Wine Guy?
保罗  那个调酒的
Oh yeah, I know Paul.
对  我认识保罗
You mean you know Paul like I know Paul?
你是说你认识他就像我认识他一样
Are you kidding? I take credit for Paul.
开玩笑吧  保罗还欠我一个人情呢
Y'know before me, there was no snap in his turtle for two years.
遇到我之前他已有两年无法过性生活
Of course it was a lie!
显然他是骗你的
Why?! Why? Why, why would anybody do something like that?
为什么  为什么会有人那样做
I assume we're looking for an answer more sophisticated
我想你是想让我们拿出一个
than 'to get you into bed'.
比"想和你上床"更为复杂的回答
Is it me?
问题出在我身上
Is it like I have some sort of beacon
难道我身上带着某种味儿
that only dogs and men with severe emotional problems can hear?
只有狗和有严重情感问题的男人才会发觉吗
All right, come here, give me your feet.
好啦  过来  把你的脚给我
I just thought he was nice, you know?
我只是以为他是个好男人
I can't believe you didn't know it was a lie!
我真不相信  你不知道那是个谎言
- Guess what?  - You got a job?
-猜猜怎么了  -你找到工作了
Are you kidding? I'm trained for nothing!
开玩笑吗  我什么都不会
I was laughed out of twelve interviews today.
今天十二个面试  我都是被嘲笑轰出来的
And yet you're surprisingly upbeat.
不过你却异常兴奋
You would be too if you found John and David boots on sale,
如果你遇见"约翰&大卫"的皮靴打五折
fifty percent off!
也会跟我一样的
Oh, how well you know me...
是呀  你多了解我啊
They're my new 'I don't need a job,
这就是  我不需要工作
I don't need my parents, I've got great boots' boots!
不需要父母  一双好皮靴足矣
How'd you pay for them?
你怎么付的款
Uh, credit card.
用信用卡
And who pays for that?
那谁付账单
Um... my... father.
我爸啊
C'mon, you can't live off your parents your whole life.
拜托  你不能靠你爸一辈子
I know that. That's why I was getting married.
我知道  这就是为什么我要结婚
Give her a break, it's hard being on your own for the first time.
饶了她吧  第一次独立并不轻松
Thank you.
谢谢
You're welcome. I remember when I first came to this city.
不客气  我记得我第一次来纽约时的情景
I was fourteen.
当时我十四岁
My mom had just killed herself and my step-dad was back in prison,
我妈刚自杀  我继父再度入狱
and I got here, and I didn't know anybody.
我来到这里  举目无亲
And I ended up living with this albino guy who was, like,
最后我和一个白化病患者住在一起
cleaning windshields outside port authority,
他给港务局的人清洗车窗玻璃
and then he killed himself,
后来他也自杀了
and then I found aromatherapy.
然后我成了按摩师
So believe me, I know exactly how you feel.
所以相信我  我完全了解你的感受
The word you're looking for is
你想要说的话是
"Anyway"...
"无论如何"
All right, you ready?
好了准备好了吗
- I don't think so.
-我不这么想
C'mon, cut. Cut, cut, cut,...
剪掉  剪掉  剪掉
Welcome to the real world!
欢迎来到现实世界
It sucks. You're gonna love it!
它糟透了  但你会喜欢的
Well, that's it. You gonna crash on the couch?
好啦  你要睡在沙发上吗
No. No, I gotta go home sometime.
不  我要回家
- You be okay?  - Yeah.
-你没事吧  -没事
Hey Mon, look what I just found on the floor.
莫妮卡  看我在地板上发现了什么
What?
什么
That's Paul's watch.
那是保罗的表
You just put it back where you found it. Oh boy
放回原地就好了
- Alright. Goodnight, everybody.  - Goodnight.
-好吧  晚安各位  -晚安
- Sorry-  - No no no, go-
-对不起  -不不  你来
No, you have it, really, I don't want it
不不  你吃吧  真的  我不想吃
- Split it?  - Okay.
-分着吃  -好吧
You know you probably didn't know this,
你大概不知道
but back in high school, I had a, um,
我在高中时  曾经
major crush on you.
暗恋过你
I knew.
我知道
You did! Oh....
你知道  哦
I always figured you just thought
我还以为你一直认为
I was Monica's geeky older brother.
我是莫妮卡的怪哥哥呢
I did.
的确如此
Oh. Listen, do you think
听着  你是不是认为
and try not to let my intense vulnerability
不要太在意我
become any kind of a factor here
脆弱的心灵
but do you think it would be okay if I asked you out?
但是你觉得我能约你出去吗
Sometime? Maybe?
偶尔  有可能吗
Yeah, maybe...
当然  或许
Okay... okay, maybe I will...
好  好  或许我会的
- Goodnight.  - Goodnight.
-晚安  -晚安
See ya....
再见
Wait, wait, hey, what's the deal?
等等  你怎么了
I just grabbed a spoon.
我刚刚拿起了勺子
I can't believe what I'm hearing here.
我真不敢相信我的耳朵
I can't believe what I'm hearing here...
What? I-I said you had a
怎么了  我说你有一个
What I said you had...
我说你有一个
Would you stop?
你能不能不这么干
- Oh, was I doing it again?  - Yes!
-噢  我又来了  -是的
Would anybody like more coffee?
有人要咖啡吗
Did you make it, or are you just serving it?
是你冲的  还是你端来的
- I'm just serving it.  - Yeah. Yeah, I'll have a cup of coffee.
-我端来的  -好吧  给我来杯咖啡
Kids, new dream...
孩子们  我又做新梦了
I'm in Las Vegas.
我在拉斯维加斯
I'm Liza Minelli-
我是丽莎·明妮莉
著名女明星